http://www.millerbrospaint.com/pages/legal-privacy

Miller Money
Overview Miller Bros Paint., is a simple business, with simple philosophies. We provide you with this privacy policy to help you understand what happens when you provide us with your information when you use or visit out site, when you do business with us, information, if any, may be gathered during your visit, and how we may use such information. By visiting our site, you signify you consent to the practices and policies in this notice.Browsing Our Site This policy applies to the information practices of Miller Bros Paint and its affiliates (collectively, "we," "us" or "our"). In general, you can browse this web site without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself. We may gather non-personal navigational information about where visitors go on our web site and information about the technical efficiencies of the site (i.e., statistics about web server activity, the type of data visitors access, referrer information, search engine performance, geographic information, browsers, platforms, server errors, items and information placed into abandoned shopping carts, and so on). We regularly analyze and use this information to deliver updated content and to support and enhance our relationship with you when you visit our site, through both advertising, keyword and press promotion. Information We Collect and How We Use It You will need to provide information about yourself if you choose to make a purchase from us, register on this site, create an account, sign up for an e-mail list or converse with us by e-mail. When you transact with us, we may collect from you personal information such as your name, billing and shipping addresses, customer service inquiries, telephone number, email address and user names or passwords for your Miller Bros Paint account. We may collect information about products, services and features that you visit or use, how frequently you use them, location data and other information about mobile devices used to access and interact with us, and your responses to any offerings or advertisements we present to you. This information will be used for fraud protection purposes, to fulfill orders, to pre-authorize or complete a sale, to respond to inquiries, to communicate with you regarding our site and services, to personalize the content and offerings to you, to conduct research about use of our sites by our users, and to provide other information that may be of interest to you. We may also collect any information about gift recipients in this same manner if this feature is active within the site.
If you have signed up to receive email offers from us and at any time you'd like to stop future delivery of these email offers, simply follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each message. Please be aware, however, that even if you request to be removed from our email marketing list, you understand and agree that we may still contact you by email regarding any orders that you place with us. How We Share Information We do not sell personal information to third parties, but may in the normal course of business, provide this information to our agents, representatives, contractors, warehouses, and service providers that help us provide services to you, such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, maintaining databases, and administering and monitoring email inquiries. We use Amazon Payments as a secure online 3rd party payments processor. You may find the Amazon Payments privacy policy at: https://payments.amazon.com/sdui/sdui/about?nodeId=82974 You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or it is necessary to protect the users of our web site, the site or the public. By using this web site, you agree that information collected on this site can be used for all purposes stated within this policy. Protecting Children Our sites and services are intended for a general audience, and children under the age of thirteen should not register without the consent of a parent or guardian. Site Security While we implement security measures on this web site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible. If you are reluctant to send information you deem sensitive over the internet, we have provided alternative options to make it easier for you to shop and purchase our products. You can telephone us M - F at (513) 531-1501 to pay by Credit Card, Check or Money Order. Should you choose the latter option send payment with Order Number indicated in the Memo field to: Miller Bros Paint, 4343 Montgomery Rd. Cincinnati, Ohio 45212. Orders will be released upon payment receipt. Use of Cookies and Other Technologies Like many websites, we also use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive and are used by us to help track clicks and pass information as you go through the pages within the web site. For example, the cookies we use allow you to add multiple items to your shopping cart and recognize items that you placed in your shopping cart in a previous browsing session. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use outside data collection tools provided from third-party sources including Google Analytics to better understand our website's metrics. To disable this type of cookie, some browsers will indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis. Data collected includes or could include search engine referrals, traffic driven by online promotions, how a visitor navigates our site, what time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, what site referred the visitor to the web page, items placed in shopping carts and which are abandoned, purchases if made in the same or multiple sessions and other miscellaneous information that may be provided through the tools you use to navigate and access this site. The collected data is analyzed on an aggregate basis and tied only to anonymous transaction totals, so it is not associated with the personal information of our visitors. We may contract with third-party service providers at our discretion. We might also use the information provided to personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. These ads are located in a green box near the bottom of each page. Google utilizes the DART cookie which enables it to serve these ads. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We use Google AdWords, a web analytics and search engine advertising campaign management service. Google AdWords uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help us analyze how users use the site. You may find Google AdWords Privacy Statement at http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html. We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help us analyze how users use the site. You may find Google Analytics Privacy Policy at http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla FireFox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly. How you remove or modify information provided to us It is not necessary to create an on-line account in order to shop with us. However, if you chose to create an account and have your information saved to permit faster shopping, checkout and order lookup but no longer desire for us to keep this information in our database you must notify us in writing to have this account information purged. Address this inquiry to Miller Bros Paint, 4343 Montgomery Rd., Cincinnati, Ohio 45212. The inclusion of current contact information is mandatory in case we have questions or need to further verify your authority to manage this information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
In order to make modifications to your online account information simply sign in using the "My Account" link at the top of any page where you may edit your password, shipping, billing and/or other pertinent information. Other Sites and Social Networks While navigating this site you will find informative links to other sites operated by third parties. We may provide you with functionality to help share information from out sites with others. These links and sharing services are provided for your convenience, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites and services. Links that appear on our website should not be deemed to imply we endorse or have any affiliation with the linked web site. We may also give you the ability to interact with us and other customers on social media sites, such as, by receiving microblogs from us, or becoming one of our fans on a social media site. Please note that these other Web sites, social media sites and sharing services collect information independently from their users, which are subject to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to review the privacy policy and data collection practices of any other web site that you visit in this manner and remind you that we will not be held responsible for the actions or practices of such web sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). FTC Disclosure We may use the services of Google, Infolinks Inc and/or Prosperent to automatically affiliate commercial links or display contextual advertising to you during your visit to one of our sites. You should know that we often times get paid if you click one of these links and/or ultimately purchase a product or service. This disclosure is provided in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission's 16 CFR 255.5: Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising. Questions and feedback We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this policy and this web site, please contact us via our website link Contact us or by postal mail at the following address: Miller Bros Paint, 4343 Montgomery Rd., Cincinnati, Ohio 45212. International Visitors
If you are visiting our web site from a location outside of the U.S., your orders placed through our web site will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from the U.S. and all information you provide will be maintained on our web servers and/or internal systems located within the U.S. and your connection will be through and to servers located in the U.S. Terms of Service Please also visit our Terms & Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. By accessing or using our sites and services, you signify that you agree to our Terms of Service. Changes to our policy As we continue to offer our visitors new and different types of content and services, we may modify our information collection and use practices. Should there be a material change to our information collection and use practices, it will be applied only to information collected on a going forward basis, and we will update this Privacy Policy. Returns
In the event you are unsatisfied with any product purchased from us, the below return policy describes the remedies available to you. Refund We will provide you with a full refund of the purchase price of the product purchased from us when there is; 1. Packing Error refund or replacement within 30 days of receipt. 2. Shipping or other product damage notice within 10 days of receipt. See below "Procedures for Sending Products Back to Us?" in order to process a return. Issued Credit In the event you wish to return a product to us for a reason other than mentioned above under "Refund" (i.e. an elective return, you changed mind, you ordered too many, you didn't like product, etc.) please note that due to the Chemical Nature of items being sold ALL SALES ARE FINAL once accepted and shipped to your location. Therefore, no return of merchandise will be accepted for any reason except as previously noted under "Refund".  If a Refund is approved, we will credit you less a 30% restock fee and the actual shipping charges we were charged to ship your order to you.Procedures for Sending Products Back to Us A Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number must be obtained before merchandise is returned to our facility.  If you do not have an account on our website you may telephone (513) 531-1501. Items returned without first obtaining an RMA will be discarded and no credit will be issued. Customer Service For assistance or questions regarding this Return Policy use the Contact Us link for fastest resolution or call us at (513) 531-1501. Thank you for your business.
Main menu
Benjamin Moore
Interior Paints & Primers
Exterior Paints & Primers
Specialty Paints & Stains
Painter Supplies
Wallpaper
Marking Paint
Join our mailing list for updates, promotions and special offers
Copyright © 2020 mbpaint.
Empire Theme by Pixel Union. Powered by Shopify
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
